Speaker #1: Hallow is likely around here somewhere.
Speaker #1: I sense he is close.
Speaker #1: Where is he?
Speaker #1: I do not know.
Speaker #1: We should look around.
Speaker #2: Too afraid to fight back.
Speaker #2: No children.
Speaker #2: You fight like a muggle little natsayoni in it and
Speaker #2: they're excruciatingly loyal companion.
Speaker #2: You 2 have done quite a bit of damage to
Speaker #2: my business interests, but I must gradually give you some
Speaker #2: credit.
Speaker #2: What was once a mere annoyance has become remarkably problematic.
Speaker #2: Fortunately, I pride myself on my problem solving skills.
Speaker #2: Come now, you can do better than that.
Speaker #1: Do you really believe that you are so proud?
Speaker #1: Nothing.
Speaker #1: No.
Speaker #2: Nothing.